Go. go. go!
I didn't get him.
There were two others there.
They were expecting us.
It doesn't matter.
They'll have to report that
he's under threat now. That's all we need.
What if he gives them
the girlfriend's address?
Then they'll get a surprise.
Meet you at the rendezvous.
Go. go. Come on.
I'm sorry.
I failed.
I told you.
all we need is for MI5 to look into him.
And you played your part.
So what now?
After Abbotsfield. we hit them again.
Bigger than the first time.
We need them to be confused and scared.
I need a hospital.
Rest.
We'll take care of you.
Where are we?
Didn't you say
you'd take me to the hospital?
Calm down.
I'm blind in one eye
and the bitch stabbed me with a needle.
And it's still in my thigh.
Control yourself.
This is a battlefield.
We've been here before.
We have to help him.
Give him something for the pain until
we can get him seen to.
You'll draw attention
if you go to the hospital.
MI5 know your injuries.
They will be looking for you.
- Where are you going?
- No. no. no.
- Are you crazy?
What the fuck? You killed him.
He was your friend. And you killed him.
He was a soldier. he knew the risks.
If you want to be a soldier.
you need to learn and understand that too.
Mum! Put the knife down.
Mum. give me... give me the knife.
give me the knife!
I'll talk to them.
Go to sleep.
Mum! Go to sleep! Bloody hell!
Ready to play your part?
What do we do about him?
We can't drive around
with a dead body in the back.
And we can't just leave him here.
He'll be identified.
No. he won't.